let's do some structure stuff okay your
ETA coaching Dasia NATO the oh she plays
that is let's do some structure stuff
but I will still try to finish early
okay just try it out tangential coaching
the nation now watching young sergeant
yes we're supposed to be talking about
the foundation 18 course blessing that
young we're trying it's just about a the
teacher by Archie not yet topic like a
tutti school is in either shape hi
famous its young K 2 T sin Hawaii
without a curse in she teaching me me me
the dementia youth hasn't been the what
your why decisions don't you find a
lasting emptiness teaching she'll come
it's insane gosh oh oh course hosting
that your integers at which came in
because she loves to show them yo yo I
found the cousin yeah oh me me the
cousin Joe show course 13 I lost half my
students how to teach this aunty the
cousin show was the chilla Watauga a
foundation now how addition city - a hot
utility enjoy watching I just the face
hands can do end up now how you homie yo
hey Lyla so that's the flow but don't so
well course where we on don't remember
Michela bgcolor we finished body stuff
about we finished a we finished death
and well maintained dalla sua and
whatnot and here no Shoshana oh yeah
another popular class so do Michael face
on zooming the curtain you're a bad
person stop doing it
Euan haha the other sure so I met the
highest Lama in the world by the way and
they asked me just review some courses
in person which also take a Chiquita to
people who don't have the table okay
which is to show you what does some
computation of the valve without a tree
to get mention your hung out
don't you mean take nasal okay if you
want to know the four nuns bells the
nuns well somebody tell me those in
Charlotte some King now you should know
how to go on all the night coming Charla
Nash yes Liotta there weren't enough
survivors I'll show her chunks there has
to be a certain number of nuns there
this year
Lyndon Johnson that that's leeway full
nun it has tirelessly you couldn't take
four nuns vows that's a joke Bernanke so
take a guess who revives and it's yet
darkness a bypass okay we did it here
she okay that just a woman to be an
older woman somebody say Hubbard them
John Brady Brady - translated thank you
go ah yeah it was very controversial
this is so cool right so this show has
synthesized by your injustice you're
doing it themselves he keeping woman
that's what I have any sitting anywhere
want to brag about the m9 well thank
John amazing summary on CUDA why written
bytes on copper okay Co don't have a
dissociate Nigel now that book is so
short
let me show Hank that's you need an
explanation okay let me see I irritation
I I decided to use one by se llama quick
so what do you think okay his name is
move to move to Quicksilver silver water
will choose a mercury which is used in
Tonto by the way in the don't give me
don't try Quicksilver and he's amazing
llama from about 300 years ago
nah so you waiting some sued he's fair
money my face how you will of they
were me young tabata summary Ciccone
passion back up on the horse 10 cents
surf surf and amazing what's it mean so
did you have a system oh yeah okay
hustle 10 five cents each okay get how
sniffing hassle gets five cents word
gets faster
just kidding Roby thoughts about it okay
yeah this subject the chief which means
that vows you have to keep to reach
nirvana
okay what's the new Panda 88 the vows of
monks nuns shopping since then you tell
me in the bank a bank
don't tell me y'all did you find I did
the Mahayana
one de bellas artes and easyJet needle
yeah we translated and we say you want a
copy for the soldier Oh Tula
if I either and it's a very sweet vow
not to get abusive face on the moon
about what other you will study in this
course and uh good most of it
okay how many oceans so we have the
commentary by
just going back difficulty Michael booty
poppin cotton honey you're
talking Tantra clinic yo Jagger
Quicksilver passionate she the needle
quicksilver's Quicksilver she felt quite
young that's what she talked about her
at the meeting huh that's a much song
with Heather laughs which is one of the
biggest subjects of Tantra so the year
should say meeting him in the hunt
attitude he wrote a little shoe
isolation found the shoe i if you ask
about Zuko needs I said what's the
potential no to the Suncheon guess it's
Amanda not in that setting you up for
casino so when you don't see me John
Thornton Bank okay
and the lesson there is a woman young
super the soon that she hadn't a don't
know what's the flow answer you're gonna
study in Tantra course you would
hostilities amines youngest always she
ate other shoe okay fine I've had any
Bashar quicksilver's haha
so you tell me time of the shooting part
of the flow oh she should DCI
versatility other cousin before you know
just razani syndrome bear how something
yeah but you cannot enter Taunton
without it Jinju can you push a t-shirt
on without a good medium frequent emails
on how the thousand for New York on 19 -
Tommy - treating other people kindly
opponent Aaron it's the basis of secret
practice okay and if you don't know but
you you gonna put it out here you go
honey twin about to punch a gamete on
why women are you wanna see angels come
to you and teach you in person you and
Shang Zuko like go tell me none mr.
de marchi don't shatter on the trees
hiring your Hummer
not your ego that sexy okay good how do
your house you're shutting me out
Bienvenue how young she doin
yeah so the main book is do a gutter
nimble hi youngsters Chanel and the
commentaries by master Yashida
you should Quicksilver to the passion
share them by the way I think I ask you
this question already shell hostage
issue another spider bite some copper to
his washing your disciple that he
banished is too bad to make 108
monasteries ii desuyo
Sheila keep on seeing of course 9
there's a second letter how the pizzas
that tsongkhapa wrote to him she gets
have a decent it's a response to a
letter that he did you shoot no not that
I made the first yeah yeah
and as a a CIT serious sensor you can
hire I can always hold the mom enough
for that always left hand down for
reasons you way you're not going to see
them dinging so any osomatsu then when
they get to course nine that all don't
want your mail question what makes good
meditation how does what she needs a
module how you treat other people needs
a module okay that's how it was
so copper don't contribution today
meditation in his Santa thousands of
pages about each handle the nature his
beloved this module Sheila daddy kicked
out even single face see either
pizza right Jasmine de ba in other
countries body love the students so much
aphasia
I have education
I'm so happy they're only because you
bothered husband was trying to focus on
interrupting other people before you
don't irritate them you don't bother
them if you have to tell them in the
evening otherwise and they'll they'll be
a wreck the next day and the next end
okay
you with us I'm sure there's always a
magician
okay general thing thoughts and she
shows us your wiseass
you got to criticize your students you
will be stopping me this yeah how many
incision like okay respect
peace of mind hi and a turn King Jeanne
good deeds is a good decision of respect
just good this list is a great way to
have good meditation and that's an
important we saw this course cool
oh yeah that's a good okay I had
something else to say about that where I
was done yeah anyway that's enough
yeah if you want your mind to be quiet
let me show you the each the painting
that seeds
opening in your mind Danny 65 per second
may now a super jumps at that pie
silence it's more than any that you
should jump that high that's what you
call good meditation did you see how you
got an a string of good seeds balances
visual King Honda satisfactions
contentment seeds all these beautiful
meditations focuses don't expect to have
water melons if you didn't plant them
well your meditations for next week this
week I know what I wanted to add say she
- well she knows sorry say it's part of
the word say okay mr. know-it-all
oh come on we've got that huh she is the
same for right sir sir same I think it
came from the same route same is food
sustenance yeah four kinds of sustenance
four things you need to eat or you will
get sick okay first one is easy
come casue funky sing yeah physical food
just physical food woman second one is
sleep shamea you want to have fun with
an employee in your company take the
nicest person in the company and don't
let them sleep for three four days
common baby kind of unit yeah it's kind
of maybe sometimes okay lack of sleep
makes anybody it doesn't matter how good
it is Amy if you don't stay for three
for days I'm sorry okay
second kind of food desert of soon see
one hope see you and what's the famous
example jerome in turkish is is among
yeah a horse
syrian desert okay who's dying of thirst
okay because they see an oasis Khandala
they will know who ever died two meters
from the water main overhang okay young
me why so much hope about just a
no horse that died two meters from the
water may ojou-sama second okay they
have the fourth kind of food nah
just focused they don't have to eat by
the way if your meditation gets a really
good need amiga here are you hallo ha
you will have this experience I predict
prediction today you'll be sitting in a
quiet place
that you didn't breathe for 10 minutes
you feel say oh my god breath is food ok
you don't need it ha focus if your focus
is strongly you don't need breath it's
very interesting
Cheeta then I take it funny thing about
you I had a yoga teacher this ok but it
has another name Kevin uh kombucha
the spontaneous stopping of your breath
no joke wasn't don't you it has a name
here so there's all these maybe you get
up to it we'll stop I didn't stop you
from breathing why are we talking about
that human being for me as much as okay
if you deprive a human being asleep
three four days I did it the nicest
person in your company will become the
biggest my teacher hates it when I
cursed by the way so don't let me curse
in the class anyway if you don't let you
all focus they were all so k so a good
way to ruin a good employee okay by
wrapping them every half hour with a
different diamond Academy like ne-yo
keep interrupting
yeah we're talking about how to plant
them about okay don't interrupt people
if your husband okay got it
and your meditation will improve the
Haitian reason that's the only cause it
doesn't matter what you glad you put our
first okay look I need some much the
best meditator on my gosh e-class
meditated on his back one night he beat
the abbot of touching number in a debate
in front of like a thousand people this
is the guy who only study on and he had
the illegal tape recorder with rock and
roll he never that's it interrupted
other people in life what you can focus
with positron Johnny Bishop is not the
posture that's the connection between
nine and class number did your car three
peace and courage in the Guardian yeah
absolutely yeah during the book help
cement it because when you do bother
other people saved you when you cannot
you can confess clay Jenkinson
Jared I mean I didn't think about it to
be honest but 9 connected a to the
baggage in the cornea schism yonder it
it's like death meditation basically
salami - not to get your own house - we
all treat down okay so I guess there's
some flowed they're gonna summon oh
what's 10 geumja
yeah so look I have 11 minutes okay oh
and jawan Jyoti shoe probably the most
important book for Bodhisattva in sight
written by shanti demo i see y'all
around 700 my letter is how does she do
that's right in the middle of inside you
don't see this all i think so
anyway so he wrote a book called buddies
okay I'm gonna tell you parents 39 I'll
tell you - turn bad South happy fourth a
blue circle yeah he had a nickname in
the monastery called boo so cool hi yo
means mr. lazy
mister do nothing missed it and so he
had a reputation in the monastery she
wasn't a good teacher you were how about
he didn't show up in the kitchen to help
house he didn't bomb about to the times
that you know basically
he seemed to be tired of feeding himself
so he said you want me to the way of
life basically a review of the ten buddy
stop four levels and the six perfections
okay basically okay so the first part
that we study in a series I taught you
just so what the tailgate died
everything is booked okay Jesse so he
God and it it's our holiday
I think surely it's the greatest body
self a book ever written even more cool
than what I'm sorry like unbelievable
incredibly based on your leader
emptiness section
you know those to do that sorta
emptiness section they have a it's
written in the in the as personal advice
how to be a bodhisattva so it's not part
of the course oh by the way you won't
know the end of this story
in the middle of the wisdom chapter
justice I see into this man and I put a
picture of it on your reading it's a
good house it's always on since Allah
and the caption if you can read the
button maybe a word will translate it
for you can you just scroll down
okay watch ah ah that's Celtic J who
wrote a great commentary go not take
just take what's it what's the last
three syllables there this is this is
him flying off just hiding face he's got
his book in his hand he's playing and
when he got deep into emptiness he
started to rise up in there and then
there were some monks in the audience
and they followed him this guy people
drop out people can't go so high it got
less and it finally they gave up and
he's still teaching it this guy and he
shattered South India he disappeared he
never came Bert how'd you say it and
it's a famous story then they had a big
meeting and oh my god okay go play havoc
in
and his antennas teaching is the best we
need to get the rest well my seller
actually said search parties to many
cities asking and they found him and
they said you know we apologize you're
actually a great master please come back
to the monastery and he said I read
decline respectfully which is another
thing about criticism right they send
another team but Kelly had the pony said
I knew you're gonna ask me made a copy
and I hid it in the roof you can find it
there okay so the next three courses
because that is so important that book
is so important for how to be a
bodhisattva
I did three courses it's 20% of a CIA
foundation courses because the last
three courses are three of the 15
courses tell me am i right so I'm gonna
do two things
I'll tell you the subjects of how I
split it up and then I'm gonna let you
out two minutes early hwacha teaching
Alvin Jung
a function good note oh I knew you'd be
happy about your enticing them you guys
think - oh let's see
by the way sure a McDonald McDaniel I'm
sorry is the registrar of a CI for like
the last 20 years
Wow Angela to go a second oh so nice oh
by the way she's the financial officer
of a large city in the United which is
amazing so we have one of the most
talented touch the UFA challenge
managers in the room and she's keeping
all your she's only 31st unions has
sensors without yeah so you should a you
should thank her new Miss B you should
get out of her good side and maybe your
grades improve okay would you like to do
them in though and we'd like to thank
you for your
[Applause]
purchasing that autumn republishing and
a camper Sun cash and no core nom de la
cha cha
he's on guard or that Nam and on the
Italian thank you sir
[Music]
my father started as a heart surgeon and
I think about 20 years ago longer
towards the beginning of the junction
[Applause]
[Music]
humming humming okay